[
  {
    "title": "Research Methodologies",
    "link": "https://www.coursera.org/learn/research-methodologies/assignment-submission/BbSlY/test-your-knowledge/attempt",
    "questionList": [
      {
        "id": 0,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~Vyf9RaU5Eeykpg69I-A1_Q@5!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~lIWsy6U5EeyZQQphaK69Fw-legend",
        "answer": ["0.8034577427548002"]
      },
      {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~Vyf9RaU5Eeykpg69I-A1_Q@5!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~HHUFiKU6Eeys6RIcgvudTw-legend",
        "answer": ["0.3104281131452382"]
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~Vyf9RaU5Eeykpg69I-A1_Q@5!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~nBKyoqU6EeyZQQphaK69Fw-legend",
        "answer": ["0.4711522786276492"]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "title": "Research Methodologies",
    "link": "https://www.coursera.org/learn/research-methodologies/assignment-submission/xa7Ys/test-your-knowledge/attempt",
    "questionList": [
      {
        "id": 0,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~oGeZMKU7EeyFOw5o8OD9Gw@4!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~sekaM6U7EeyJLw6OLoou2w-legend",
        "answer": ["0.02660013603788336"]
      },
      {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~oGeZMKU7EeyFOw5o8OD9Gw@4!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~kSfUmKU8EeyJLw6OLoou2w-legend",
        "answer": ["0.4002038197726374"]
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~oGeZMKU7EeyFOw5o8OD9Gw@4!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~Bp4EqKU9EeyJLw6OLoou2w-legend",
        "answer": ["0.898390547291088"]
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~oGeZMKU7EeyFOw5o8OD9Gw@4!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~S98Nq6U9EeyJLw6OLoou2w-legend",
        "answer": ["0.465192202004471"]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "title": "Research Methodologies",
    "link": "https://www.coursera.org/learn/research-methodologies/assignment-submission/wPH7f/test-your-knowledge/attempt",
    "questionList": [
      {
        "id": 0,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~cuG_s6VAEeyqaQphq-htLQ@5!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~h4Z6j6VAEeys6RIcgvudTw-legend",
        "answer": ["0.07702688098309785"]
      },
      {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~cuG_s6VAEeyqaQphq-htLQ@5!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~C-mfmqVBEeys6RIcgvudTw-legend",
        "answer": ["0.14997200588626547"]
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~cuG_s6VAEeyqaQphq-htLQ@5!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~Ml5w0qVBEeyZQQphaK69Fw-legend",
        "answer": ["0.5757309801613562"]
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~cuG_s6VAEeyqaQphq-htLQ@5!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~PI1nY6VBEeyJLw6OLoou2w-legend",
        "answer": ["0.6333817602718943"]
      },
      {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~cuG_s6VAEeyqaQphq-htLQ@5!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~YgsISKVBEeys6RIcgvudTw-legend",
        "answer": ["0.081701963135971"]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "title": "Research Methodologies",
    "link": "https://www.coursera.org/learn/research-methodologies/assignment-submission/z2qZf/refresh-your-knowledge/attempt",
    "questionList": [
      {
        "id": 0,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~cLcfDaU9EeywaRJXLCrIEQ@4!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~eaeiy6U9EeyZQQphaK69Fw-legend",
        "answer": ["0.43261638203918196"]
      },
      {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~cLcfDaU9EeywaRJXLCrIEQ@4!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~jD_rWqU9EeyJLw6OLoou2w-legend",
        "answer": ["0.1715657750283588"]
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~cLcfDaU9EeywaRJXLCrIEQ@4!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~tyz-VaU9Eeys6RIcgvudTw-legend",
        "answer": ["0.40074869385838663"]
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~cLcfDaU9EeywaRJXLCrIEQ@4!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~4VMYi6U9EeyZQQphaK69Fw-legend",
        "answer": ["0.058999550965934455"]
      },
      {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~cLcfDaU9EeywaRJXLCrIEQ@4!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~9o6UpaU9EeyJLw6OLoou2w-legend",
        "answer": ["0.10672246373293492"]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "title": "Research Methodologies",
    "link": "https://www.coursera.org/learn/research-methodologies/assignment-submission/Bre5i/refresh-your-knowledge/attempt",
    "questionList": [
      {
        "id": 0,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~pYl5b6VBEeykpg69I-A1_Q@3!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~DnLGRqVCEeyZQQphaK69Fw-legend",
        "answer": ["0.19975764400030083"]
      },
      {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~pYl5b6VBEeykpg69I-A1_Q@3!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~KXwCAqVCEeyJLw6OLoou2w-legend",
        "answer": ["0.587784312074835"]
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~pYl5b6VBEeykpg69I-A1_Q@3!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~Ty3RPKVCEeys6RIcgvudTw-legend",
        "answer": ["0.21291073078056533"]
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~pYl5b6VBEeykpg69I-A1_Q@3!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~kQpSZKVCEeys6RIcgvudTw-legend",
        "answer": ["0.981891901220151"]
      },
      {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~pYl5b6VBEeykpg69I-A1_Q@3!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~uHeNoqVCEeys6RIcgvudTw-legend",
        "answer": ["0.7094302883153458"]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "title": "Research Methodologies",
    "link": "https://www.coursera.org/learn/research-methodologies/assignment-submission/bt41G/test-your-knowledge/attempt",
    "questionList": [
      {
        "id": 0,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~L_fCc6VHEeyrdhKkPbxjLw@4!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~PUxjOaVHEeyZQQphaK69Fw-legend",
        "answer": ["0.18511813893650664"]
      },
      {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~L_fCc6VHEeyrdhKkPbxjLw@4!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~mMH2l7mFEey6SRJD0KD-Hw-legend",
        "answer": ["0.6845080156959964"]
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~L_fCc6VHEeyrdhKkPbxjLw@4!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~A7Hz8rmHEey6SRJD0KD-Hw-legend",
        "answer": ["0.1754881485981752"]
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~L_fCc6VHEeyrdhKkPbxjLw@4!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~G4vJu6XMEey8QhIWFP13eQ-legend",
        "answer": ["0.3863881338056594"]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "title": "Research Methodologies",
    "link": "https://www.coursera.org/learn/research-methodologies/assignment-submission/oJdlg/test-your-knowledge/attempt",
    "questionList": [
      {
        "id": 0,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~o-SHeaXWEeyFOw5o8OD9Gw@6!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~UI6gV7mWEey1rg5035t4iw-legend",
        "answer": ["0.6413758552486748"]
      },
      {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~o-SHeaXWEeyFOw5o8OD9Gw@6!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~kszwTrmWEey6SRJD0KD-Hw-legend",
        "answer": ["0.6893732454983914"]
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~o-SHeaXWEeyFOw5o8OD9Gw@6!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~vzULLLmWEeyrqgpnhQwcew-legend",
        "answer": ["0.5321896356871725"]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "title": "Research Methodologies",
    "link": "https://www.coursera.org/learn/research-methodologies/assignment-submission/iIw2O/test-your-knowledge/attempt",
    "questionList": [
      {
        "id": 0,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~21KPiaVFEeyrdhKkPbxjLw@4!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~HFwMN7dKEeyowBLlXFZoQw-legend",
        "answer": ["0.6731453557653033"]
      },
      {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~21KPiaVFEeyrdhKkPbxjLw@4!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~lhmq1bdKEeyowBLlXFZoQw-legend",
        "answer": ["0.706660754231957"]
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~21KPiaVFEeyrdhKkPbxjLw@4!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~1lBrO7dKEeyowBLlXFZoQw-legend",
        "answer": ["0.6820572870006056"]
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~21KPiaVFEeyrdhKkPbxjLw@4!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~QF0CE7dLEeyNxgoF0jGcZw-legend",
        "answer": ["0.7015752333621494"]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "title": "Research Methodologies",
    "link": "https://www.coursera.org/learn/research-methodologies/assignment-submission/8Lzhh/refresh-your-knowledge/attempt",
    "questionList": [
      {
        "id": 0,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~7noMGKXMEeylUBKfIKrhyQ@4!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~B5JOKKXNEey8QhIWFP13eQ-legend",
        "answer": ["0.7709579113126266"]
      },
      {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~7noMGKXMEeylUBKfIKrhyQ@4!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~WYF956XNEeyZQQphaK69Fw-legend",
        "answer": ["0.7361141818989427"]
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~7noMGKXMEeylUBKfIKrhyQ@4!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~sPXMT6XNEeyZQQphaK69Fw-legend",
        "answer": ["0.9554588153529626"]
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~7noMGKXMEeylUBKfIKrhyQ@4!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~TqhvLqXOEey8QhIWFP13eQ-legend",
        "answer": ["0.2590318325760952"]
      },
      {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~7noMGKXMEeylUBKfIKrhyQ@4!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~fMf97aXOEeyKZQ5FNpii9Q-legend",
        "answer": ["0.76166595649241"]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "title": "Research Methodologies",
    "link": "https://www.coursera.org/learn/research-methodologies/assignment-submission/5c3pw/test-your-knowledge/attempt",
    "questionList": [
      {
        "id": 0,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~GzlnFKXQEey1egrW0Q9-6w@3!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~ivRDH7mHEey6SRJD0KD-Hw-legend",
        "answer": ["0.9103970220691109"]
      },
      {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~GzlnFKXQEey1egrW0Q9-6w@3!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~lrgDWLmKEeyrqgpnhQwcew-legend",
        "answer": ["0.304225973059316"]
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~GzlnFKXQEey1egrW0Q9-6w@3!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~-mu1Z7mOEey1rg5035t4iw-legend",
        "answer": ["0.4072004437761718"]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "title": "Research Methodologies",
    "link": "https://www.coursera.org/learn/research-methodologies/assignment-submission/oql7F/refresh-your-knowledge/attempt",
    "questionList": [
      {
        "id": 0,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~Z9P7QaXXEeywaRJXLCrIEQ@2!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~gkpte6XXEeyZQQphaK69Fw-legend",
        "answer": ["0.9022832625968304"]
      },
      {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~Z9P7QaXXEeywaRJXLCrIEQ@2!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~MD_3gaXYEeyKZQ5FNpii9Q-legend",
        "answer": ["0.7857022475805662"]
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~Z9P7QaXXEeywaRJXLCrIEQ@2!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~ZvhywqXYEeyZQQphaK69Fw-legend",
        "answer": ["0.9584610956713608"]
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~Z9P7QaXXEeywaRJXLCrIEQ@2!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~fP319KXYEeyZQQphaK69Fw-legend",
        "answer": ["0.2167021069852555"]
      },
      {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~Z9P7QaXXEeywaRJXLCrIEQ@2!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~oETgE6XYEeyZQQphaK69Fw-legend",
        "answer": ["0.49435207138691784"]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "title": "Research Methodologies",
    "link": "https://www.coursera.org/learn/research-methodologies/assignment-submission/67kNR/test-your-knowledge/attempt",
    "questionList": [
      {
        "id": 0,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~M6aSpKXeEeyRAAqqmepzlw@5!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~VAGBBaXeEeyZQQphaK69Fw-legend",
        "answer": ["0.7014100355722697"]
      },
      {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~M6aSpKXeEeyRAAqqmepzlw@5!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~KQjNDLmZEeyrqgpnhQwcew-legend",
        "answer": ["0.5868288896739877"]
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~M6aSpKXeEeyRAAqqmepzlw@5!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~WxSJsLmZEey1rg5035t4iw-legend",
        "answer": ["0.982697754733457"]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "title": "Research Methodologies",
    "link": "https://www.coursera.org/learn/research-methodologies/assignment-submission/DndWc/test-your-knowledge/attempt",
    "questionList": [
      {
        "id": 0,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~FVJVqqXfEeyfpQ6aqrv_Ww@4!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~oDrdyLmZEeyrqgpnhQwcew-legend",
        "answer": ["0.5800335398395038"]
      },
      {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~FVJVqqXfEeyfpQ6aqrv_Ww@4!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~UpE1ArmbEeyrqgpnhQwcew-legend",
        "answer": ["0.5199774236738162"]
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~FVJVqqXfEeyfpQ6aqrv_Ww@4!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~srgTSbmbEey1rg5035t4iw-legend",
        "answer": ["0.37216134901798625"]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "title": "Research Methodologies",
    "link": "https://www.coursera.org/learn/research-methodologies/assignment-submission/R9B5r/test-your-knowledge/attempt",
    "questionList": [
      {
        "id": 0,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~kxfOFqXkEeyqlwqX9Wfusw@4!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~d6tiVbmcEey1rg5035t4iw-legend",
        "answer": ["0.8650843335743812"]
      },
      {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~kxfOFqXkEeyqlwqX9Wfusw@4!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~wvVe57mcEey6SRJD0KD-Hw-legend",
        "answer": ["0.13317379912130645"]
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~kxfOFqXkEeyqlwqX9Wfusw@4!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~edkFwLmeEeyrqgpnhQwcew-legend",
        "answer": ["0.1550934299639366"]
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~kxfOFqXkEeyqlwqX9Wfusw@4!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~tFnUQbmeEey1rg5035t4iw-legend",
        "answer": ["0.2677303707494727"]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "title": "Research Methodologies",
    "link": "https://www.coursera.org/learn/research-methodologies/assignment-submission/7anX9/test-your-knowledge/attempt",
    "questionList": [
      {
        "id": 0,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~nFBhJaXlEeyJTg7wZPKy3w@3!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~6eW3J7meEeyrqgpnhQwcew-legend",
        "answer": ["0.39085566315504705"]
      },
      {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~nFBhJaXlEeyJTg7wZPKy3w@3!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~b7KlWbmfEey1rg5035t4iw-legend",
        "answer": ["0.421485808065136"]
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~nFBhJaXlEeyJTg7wZPKy3w@3!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~M4uOsbmhEeyrqgpnhQwcew-legend",
        "answer": ["0.63678328716181"]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "title": "Research Methodologies",
    "link": "https://www.coursera.org/learn/research-methodologies/assignment-submission/Qe6kH/refresh-your-knowledge/attempt",
    "questionList": [
      {
        "id": 0,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~lGSLpaXfEeyFOw5o8OD9Gw@2!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~phgZqqXfEey8QhIWFP13eQ-legend",
        "answer": ["0.3702890659919429"]
      },
      {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~lGSLpaXfEeyFOw5o8OD9Gw@2!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~5iBQEKXfEey8QhIWFP13eQ-legend",
        "answer": ["0.9061297218676607"]
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~lGSLpaXfEeyFOw5o8OD9Gw@2!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~yFcUUaXgEeyKZQ5FNpii9Q-legend",
        "answer": ["0.9913910615042778"]
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~lGSLpaXfEeyFOw5o8OD9Gw@2!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~48NXZaXgEey8QhIWFP13eQ-legend",
        "answer": ["0.09358649671069763"]
      },
      {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~lGSLpaXfEeyFOw5o8OD9Gw@2!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~XJUPZ6XhEeyZQQphaK69Fw-legend",
        "answer": ["0.8167738645598583"]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "title": "Research Methodologies",
    "link": "https://www.coursera.org/learn/research-methodologies/assignment-submission/vAMkt/refresh-your-knowledge/attempt",
    "questionList": [
      {
        "id": 0,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~scZ2WaXlEeyfpQ6aqrv_Ww@2!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~0gvhw7mhEey6SRJD0KD-Hw-legend",
        "answer": ["0.30841477997439926"]
      },
      {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~scZ2WaXlEeyfpQ6aqrv_Ww@2!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~dBi3OrmiEey6SRJD0KD-Hw-legend",
        "answer": ["0.7877043327666571"]
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~scZ2WaXlEeyfpQ6aqrv_Ww@2!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~lZ0xD7miEey1rg5035t4iw-legend",
        "answer": ["0.5479641722125421"]
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~scZ2WaXlEeyfpQ6aqrv_Ww@2!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~uercyLmiEeyrqgpnhQwcew-legend",
        "answer": ["0.8890637606997418"]
      },
      {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~scZ2WaXlEeyfpQ6aqrv_Ww@2!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~3Gni1LmiEey6SRJD0KD-Hw-legend",
        "answer": ["0.9224074389544208"]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "title": "Research Methodologies",
    "link": "https://www.coursera.org/learn/research-methodologies/assignment-submission/qffNY/test-your-knowledge/attempt",
    "questionList": [
      {
        "id": 0,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~PRzR8aXnEeyJTg7wZPKy3w@3!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~EbEbiLmjEey6SRJD0KD-Hw-legend",
        "answer": ["0.5508431218275911"]
      },
      {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~PRzR8aXnEeyJTg7wZPKy3w@3!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~4LVdTrmkEey1rg5035t4iw-legend",
        "answer": ["0.02467029857565528"]
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~PRzR8aXnEeyJTg7wZPKy3w@3!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~Dfq4JrmlEey6SRJD0KD-Hw-legend",
        "answer": ["0.22920518709963766"]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "title": "Research Methodologies",
    "link": "https://www.coursera.org/learn/research-methodologies/assignment-submission/zL89Y/test-your-knowledge/attempt",
    "questionList": [
      {
        "id": 0,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~zUF0GqXnEeylUBKfIKrhyQ@3!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~SbQG6bmlEeyrqgpnhQwcew-legend",
        "answer": ["0.31223678082816786"]
      },
      {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~zUF0GqXnEeylUBKfIKrhyQ@3!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~pyWwPLmlEey6SRJD0KD-Hw-legend",
        "answer": ["0.7748799695527613"]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "title": "Research Methodologies",
    "link": "https://www.coursera.org/learn/research-methodologies/assignment-submission/rvToF/test-your-knowledge/attempt",
    "questionList": [
      {
        "id": 0,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~Fsrfk6XpEeylUBKfIKrhyQ@3!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~xtSJlLmmEeyrqgpnhQwcew-legend",
        "answer": ["0.7305996751169073"]
      },
      {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~Fsrfk6XpEeylUBKfIKrhyQ@3!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~HktJJbmnEey1rg5035t4iw-legend",
        "answer": ["0.6016760391064151"]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "title": "Research Methodologies",
    "link": "https://www.coursera.org/learn/research-methodologies/assignment-submission/qDnMY/test-your-knowledge/attempt",
    "questionList": [
      {
        "id": 0,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~aWOhKKXqEeyfpQ6aqrv_Ww@4!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~XCUtl7mnEeyrqgpnhQwcew-legend",
        "answer": ["0.07550158718189559"]
      },
      {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~aWOhKKXqEeyfpQ6aqrv_Ww@4!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~vt3acLmnEey6SRJD0KD-Hw-legend",
        "answer": ["0.9935778579668098"]
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~aWOhKKXqEeyfpQ6aqrv_Ww@4!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~7XgXaLmnEey1rg5035t4iw-legend",
        "answer": ["0.9706426627234435"]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "title": "Research Methodologies",
    "link": "https://www.coursera.org/learn/research-methodologies/assignment-submission/DBVCK/refresh-your-knowledge/attempt",
    "questionList": [
      {
        "id": 0,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~3Ss_EKXnEeyqlwqX9Wfusw@3!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~32FJCrmlEey1rg5035t4iw-legend",
        "answer": ["0.3297863534426224"]
      },
      {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~3Ss_EKXnEeyqlwqX9Wfusw@3!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~HgeldLmmEey1rg5035t4iw-legend",
        "answer": ["0.4951808688851784"]
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~3Ss_EKXnEeyqlwqX9Wfusw@3!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~SO4CormmEey6SRJD0KD-Hw-legend",
        "answer": ["0.9820581387696081"]
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~3Ss_EKXnEeyqlwqX9Wfusw@3!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~aqgxkbmmEey1rg5035t4iw-legend",
        "answer": ["0.9096230202677347"]
      },
      {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~3Ss_EKXnEeyqlwqX9Wfusw@3!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~lGlupLmmEey6SRJD0KD-Hw-legend",
        "answer": ["0.55664076445414"]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "title": "Being a researcher (in Information Science and Technology)",
    "link": "https://www.coursera.org/learn/being-researcher/assignment-submission/P6D0g/weekly-quiz-1/attempt",
    "questionList": [
      {
        "id": 0,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~boaeC3iuEeqkJhKYONp7VQ@6!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~SBbnX4hrEeqpoQp9_OWo-Q-legend",
        "answer": ["0.39726660438017336"]
      },
      {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~boaeC3iuEeqkJhKYONp7VQ@6!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~kk3Q9YhsEeqKOBLzdzautw-legend",
        "answer": ["0.5659484272686843", "0.7234112708026013"]
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~boaeC3iuEeqkJhKYONp7VQ@6!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~yy2_0IhsEeqKOBLzdzautw-legend",
        "answer": ["0.4631345072345041", "0.08592270513117195"]
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~boaeC3iuEeqkJhKYONp7VQ@6!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~CWK9WYhtEeqpoQp9_OWo-Q-legend",
        "answer": ["0.2987754231926447", "0.033896224031308986"]
      },
      {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~boaeC3iuEeqkJhKYONp7VQ@6!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~cvOUXIhtEeqKOBLzdzautw-legend",
        "answer": ["0.43711566289141635", "0.6744705927864076"]
      },
      {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~boaeC3iuEeqkJhKYONp7VQ@6!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~uJ0ipYhtEeqpoQp9_OWo-Q-legend",
        "answer": ["0.412221822075326"]
      },
      {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~boaeC3iuEeqkJhKYONp7VQ@6!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~4RkPQYhtEeqKOBLzdzautw-legend",
        "answer": ["0.9872798816035324", "0.885378594397878"]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "title": "Being a researcher (in Information Science and Technology)",
    "link": "https://www.coursera.org/learn/being-researcher/assignment-submission/ltwHH/weekly-quiz-2/attempt",
    "questionList": [
      {
        "id": 0,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~dNkS-4hsEeqECgqX4_EeXw@3!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~daA6I4h0EeqpoQp9_OWo-Q-legend",
        "answer": ["0.5292082741083519"]
      },
      {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~dNkS-4hsEeqECgqX4_EeXw@3!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~9C4qaYkmEeqRQxI-J60NwQ-legend",
        "answer": ["0.03921918119486234"]
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~dNkS-4hsEeqECgqX4_EeXw@3!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~ZzDqSYknEeqpVw7gdp9Rzw-legend",
        "answer": ["0.7357972893930844"]
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~dNkS-4hsEeqECgqX4_EeXw@3!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~om4DGYknEeqRQxI-J60NwQ-legend",
        "answer": [
          "0.7274049043493087",
          "0.9642958089344995",
          "0.4291061979666073"
        ]
      },
      {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~dNkS-4hsEeqECgqX4_EeXw@3!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~5Slym4knEeqRQxI-J60NwQ-legend",
        "answer": ["0.7479768549628656", "0.6752856290692071"]
      },
      {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~dNkS-4hsEeqECgqX4_EeXw@3!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~cgZkU4koEeqpVw7gdp9Rzw-legend",
        "answer": [
          "0.8499782973424219",
          "0.957686566011223",
          "0.18665685676707966"
        ]
      },
      {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~dNkS-4hsEeqECgqX4_EeXw@3!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~pp_Q-4koEeqRQxI-J60NwQ-legend",
        "answer": ["0.5726831331720117", "0.9676491788151902"]
      },
      {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~dNkS-4hsEeqECgqX4_EeXw@3!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~3vyuJIkoEeqRQxI-J60NwQ-legend",
        "answer": [
          "0.41130444371525643",
          "0.860696706345079",
          "0.6355248275304195",
          "0.5501133844790862"
        ]
      },
      {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~dNkS-4hsEeqECgqX4_EeXw@3!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~3E7WO4kpEeqRQxI-J60NwQ-legend",
        "answer": ["0.3660294422259598", "0.7479840085583507"]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "title": "Being a researcher (in Information Science and Technology)",
    "link": "https://www.coursera.org/learn/being-researcher/assignment-submission/EDkz4/weekly-quiz-3/attempt",
    "questionList": [
      {
        "id": 0,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~Vwrs-3i8EeqkJhKYONp7VQ@5!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~rNf7qIoaEeq3gA6hr2H-kQ-legend",
        "answer": ["0.8884001542450979"]
      },
      {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~Vwrs-3i8EeqkJhKYONp7VQ@5!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~YEwNe4kqEeqpVw7gdp9Rzw-legend",
        "answer": ["0.6654914714455924"]
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~Vwrs-3i8EeqkJhKYONp7VQ@5!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~stI0JIkvEeqRQxI-J60NwQ-legend",
        "answer": ["0.7530396833783852", "0.6765555309015594"]
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~Vwrs-3i8EeqkJhKYONp7VQ@5!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~_wgXiokvEeqRQxI-J60NwQ-legend",
        "answer": ["0.09381212920378723", "0.6644933005586966"]
      },
      {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~Vwrs-3i8EeqkJhKYONp7VQ@5!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~PoIXqokwEeqRQxI-J60NwQ-legend",
        "answer": ["0.7955109126903541", "0.9699397042175506"]
      },
      {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~Vwrs-3i8EeqkJhKYONp7VQ@5!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~f-MnSIkwEeqRQxI-J60NwQ-legend",
        "answer": [
          "0.9676648758201958",
          "0.7401476792469994",
          "0.7880017808926654"
        ]
      },
      {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~Vwrs-3i8EeqkJhKYONp7VQ@5!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~vwIPG4kwEeqRQxI-J60NwQ-legend",
        "answer": [
          "0.3316766368721209",
          "0.9834371201718586",
          "0.1475298792390236"
        ]
      },
      {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~Vwrs-3i8EeqkJhKYONp7VQ@5!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~AMzc9YkxEeqpVw7gdp9Rzw-legend",
        "answer": ["0.47781026331836984"]
      },
      {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~Vwrs-3i8EeqkJhKYONp7VQ@5!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~UWOpiokxEeqRQxI-J60NwQ-legend",
        "answer": ["0.31556779105469945", "0.7267904550494808"]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "title": "Being a researcher (in Information Science and Technology)",
    "link": "https://www.coursera.org/learn/being-researcher/assignment-submission/0SLlP/weekly-quiz-4/attempt",
    "questionList": [
      {
        "id": 0,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~rvZngni8EeqVyA6v0tedXQ@6!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~6KqQfYk3EeqpVw7gdp9Rzw-legend",
        "answer": [
          "0.40317094599519776",
          "0.5686795072719328",
          "0.47794573936404317"
        ]
      },
      {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~rvZngni8EeqVyA6v0tedXQ@6!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~FItRiYk4EeqpVw7gdp9Rzw-legend",
        "answer": [
          "0.4857898457197254",
          "0.5048361259739111",
          "0.9362570260800283"
        ]
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~rvZngni8EeqVyA6v0tedXQ@6!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~Su7P0Ik4EeqRQxI-J60NwQ-legend",
        "answer": [
          "0.8227762400714378",
          "0.901082966639529",
          "0.5870426877761274"
        ]
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~rvZngni8EeqVyA6v0tedXQ@6!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~fYdjR4k4EeqRQxI-J60NwQ-legend",
        "answer": ["0.8986339081363184", "0.2607644920497707"]
      },
      {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~rvZngni8EeqVyA6v0tedXQ@6!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~uGmLwok4EeqRQxI-J60NwQ-legend",
        "answer": [
          "0.4144461990521797",
          "0.7793754437929405",
          "0.09995939038508728"
        ]
      },
      {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~rvZngni8EeqVyA6v0tedXQ@6!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~2vUVDYk4EeqpVw7gdp9Rzw-legend",
        "answer": [
          "0.6201690164332245",
          "0.5247157413348231",
          "0.8820600426759542"
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "title": "Being a researcher (in Information Science and Technology)",
    "link": "https://www.coursera.org/learn/being-researcher/assignment-submission/VGLhb/weekly-quiz-5/attempt",
    "questionList": [
      {
        "id": 0,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~Fh3gMHi9Eeq9HA5Jy0jLxw@5!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~l0aeH4k5EeqRQxI-J60NwQ-legend",
        "answer": [
          "0.684089607838934",
          "0.10299746147826627",
          "0.1495522913591627",
          "0.09487261399253044"
        ]
      },
      {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~Fh3gMHi9Eeq9HA5Jy0jLxw@5!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~5ZfKYIk6EeqpVw7gdp9Rzw-legend",
        "answer": ["0.7573387666509108"]
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~Fh3gMHi9Eeq9HA5Jy0jLxw@5!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~FDtV6ok7EeqpVw7gdp9Rzw-legend",
        "answer": ["0.5536523006721286", "0.15486304333648415"]
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~Fh3gMHi9Eeq9HA5Jy0jLxw@5!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~VpHpTYk7EeqRQxI-J60NwQ-legend",
        "answer": ["0.6854901284462767"]
      },
      {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~Fh3gMHi9Eeq9HA5Jy0jLxw@5!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~jlIQRok7EeqRQxI-J60NwQ-legend",
        "answer": ["0.354974687119636", "0.13136914203850125"]
      },
      {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~Fh3gMHi9Eeq9HA5Jy0jLxw@5!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~y8XgMIk7EeqRQxI-J60NwQ-legend",
        "answer": ["0.8649855805481765"]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "title": "Being a researcher (in Information Science and Technology)",
    "link": "https://www.coursera.org/learn/being-researcher/assignment-submission/mAmLV/weekly-quiz-6/attempt",
    "questionList": [
      {
        "id": 0,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~PA6NSXi9EeqVyA6v0tedXQ@10!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~JPp8CIk8EeqpVw7gdp9Rzw-legend",
        "answer": [
          "0.6110004768447841",
          "0.2617615159952036",
          "0.831234349423523"
        ]
      },
      {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~PA6NSXi9EeqVyA6v0tedXQ@10!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~Uz5bnIk8EeqRQxI-J60NwQ-legend",
        "answer": [
          "0.5250101413166466",
          "0.9968300802553669",
          "0.7677605548229796"
        ]
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~PA6NSXi9EeqVyA6v0tedXQ@10!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~g_eAfok8EeqpVw7gdp9Rzw-legend",
        "answer": ["0.04855296516371643"]
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~PA6NSXi9EeqVyA6v0tedXQ@10!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~nMG2-4k-EeqpVw7gdp9Rzw-legend",
        "answer": [
          "0.2849583171760999",
          "0.3650231611621453",
          "0.7779882635300999",
          "0.8791425731058582"
        ]
      },
      {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~PA6NSXi9EeqVyA6v0tedXQ@10!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~mKYa44lGEeqRQxI-J60NwQ-legend",
        "answer": ["0.7317604662899493"]
      },
      {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~PA6NSXi9EeqVyA6v0tedXQ@10!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~9n2yIolGEeqRQxI-J60NwQ-legend",
        "answer": ["0.2938986979588041"]
      },
      {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~PA6NSXi9EeqVyA6v0tedXQ@10!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~DmabTolHEeqRQxI-J60NwQ-legend",
        "answer": ["0.1279819572241494"]
      },
      {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~PA6NSXi9EeqVyA6v0tedXQ@10!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~Hfe-DIlHEeqpVw7gdp9Rzw-legend",
        "answer": ["0.6640563619121047"]
      },
      {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~PA6NSXi9EeqVyA6v0tedXQ@10!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~NEmMd4lHEeqpVw7gdp9Rzw-legend",
        "answer": ["0.5639217234945586"]
      },
      {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~PA6NSXi9EeqVyA6v0tedXQ@10!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~yPbEnYlHEeqpVw7gdp9Rzw-legend",
        "answer": ["0.29815034245746674"]
      },
      {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~PA6NSXi9EeqVyA6v0tedXQ@10!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~6bIhcolHEeqRQxI-J60NwQ-legend",
        "answer": ["0.8939721911106697"]
      },
      {
        "id": 11,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~PA6NSXi9EeqVyA6v0tedXQ@10!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~9t8WcolHEeqpVw7gdp9Rzw-legend",
        "answer": ["0.16335952946020793"]
      },
      {
        "id": 12,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~PA6NSXi9EeqVyA6v0tedXQ@10!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~CHH80IlIEeqRQxI-J60NwQ-legend",
        "answer": ["0.2357378196340485"]
      },
      {
        "id": 13,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~PA6NSXi9EeqVyA6v0tedXQ@10!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~FrCv84lIEeqpVw7gdp9Rzw-legend",
        "answer": ["0.1102645433542333"]
      },
      {
        "id": 14,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~PA6NSXi9EeqVyA6v0tedXQ@10!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~Ofg15YlIEeqRQxI-J60NwQ-legend",
        "answer": ["0.21820248592906344"]
      },
      {
        "id": 15,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~PA6NSXi9EeqVyA6v0tedXQ@10!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~TxOAk4lIEeqpVw7gdp9Rzw-legend",
        "answer": ["0.32094724169415545"]
      },
      {
        "id": 16,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~PA6NSXi9EeqVyA6v0tedXQ@10!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~Z9YA4YlIEeqpVw7gdp9Rzw-legend",
        "answer": ["0.7302711628436229"]
      },
      {
        "id": 17,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~PA6NSXi9EeqVyA6v0tedXQ@10!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~cB0k5YlIEeqpVw7gdp9Rzw-legend",
        "answer": ["0.704998766404449"]
      },
      {
        "id": 18,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~PA6NSXi9EeqVyA6v0tedXQ@10!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~fwcLvIlIEeqpVw7gdp9Rzw-legend",
        "answer": ["0.33841569249110814"]
      },
      {
        "id": 19,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~PA6NSXi9EeqVyA6v0tedXQ@10!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~5VGo_ontEeq3gA6hr2H-kQ-legend",
        "answer": ["0.47334492808011186"]
      },
      {
        "id": 20,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~PA6NSXi9EeqVyA6v0tedXQ@10!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~Bq4oConuEeq-9wqdHhZNuw-legend",
        "answer": ["0.0159512874752068"]
      },
      {
        "id": 21,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~PA6NSXi9EeqVyA6v0tedXQ@10!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~I5du3InuEeq3gA6hr2H-kQ-legend",
        "answer": ["0.8072479238918073"]
      },
      {
        "id": 22,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~PA6NSXi9EeqVyA6v0tedXQ@10!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~Or4ZRInuEeq-9wqdHhZNuw-legend",
        "answer": ["0.3408304835134859"]
      },
      {
        "id": 23,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~PA6NSXi9EeqVyA6v0tedXQ@10!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~Pcdh2InuEeq3gA6hr2H-kQ-legend",
        "answer": ["0.8727462713522898"]
      },
      {
        "id": 24,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~PA6NSXi9EeqVyA6v0tedXQ@10!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~8BWXq4nuEeq-9wqdHhZNuw-legend",
        "answer": ["0.9708542086387619"]
      },
      {
        "id": 25,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~PA6NSXi9EeqVyA6v0tedXQ@10!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~-8WJX4nuEeq3gA6hr2H-kQ-legend",
        "answer": ["0.21464624356228024"]
      },
      {
        "id": 26,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~PA6NSXi9EeqVyA6v0tedXQ@10!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~CbP5BonvEeq-9wqdHhZNuw-legend",
        "answer": ["0.705535866251231"]
      },
      {
        "id": 27,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~PA6NSXi9EeqVyA6v0tedXQ@10!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~HJOrI4nvEeq-9wqdHhZNuw-legend",
        "answer": ["0.7581013897845523"]
      },
      {
        "id": 28,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~PA6NSXi9EeqVyA6v0tedXQ@10!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~K4BRSYnvEeq3gA6hr2H-kQ-legend",
        "answer": ["0.9458034270473397"]
      },
      {
        "id": 29,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~PA6NSXi9EeqVyA6v0tedXQ@10!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~cxl7CInvEeq3gA6hr2H-kQ-legend",
        "answer": ["0.07237396860892731"]
      },
      {
        "id": 30,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~PA6NSXi9EeqVyA6v0tedXQ@10!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~gdlrgInvEeq-9wqdHhZNuw-legend",
        "answer": ["0.6853329990981012"]
      },
      {
        "id": 31,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~PA6NSXi9EeqVyA6v0tedXQ@10!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~kX6MNonvEeq3gA6hr2H-kQ-legend",
        "answer": ["0.980881391800823"]
      },
      {
        "id": 32,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~PA6NSXi9EeqVyA6v0tedXQ@10!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~t3PMeInvEeq3gA6hr2H-kQ-legend",
        "answer": ["0.6245205957190654"]
      },
      {
        "id": 33,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~PA6NSXi9EeqVyA6v0tedXQ@10!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~yz-0JInvEeq-9wqdHhZNuw-legend",
        "answer": ["0.7941930773304313"]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "title": "Advanced Writing",
    "link": "https://www.coursera.org/learn/advanced-writing/exam/DzuJn/advanced-argument-quiz/attempt",
    "questionList": [
      {
        "id": 0,
        "question": "MkMGO27ZEeWdpQowNaOR9w@0-legend",
        "answer": ["0.7277742421720177"]
      },
      {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "7vZrrnHJEeWFORLZt5AZxw@0-legend",
        "answer": ["0.6401299147401005"]
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "O0FdZ3HKEeWi2w6r_80vcQ@0-legend",
        "answer": ["0.6858923027757555"]
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "2BYG9nHLEeWi2w6r_80vcQ@0-legend",
        "answer": ["0.4616967854090035"]
      },
      {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "5RbBhHHTEeWFORLZt5AZxw@0-legend",
        "answer": ["0.0031197729986160994"]
      },
      {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "e5bWlXHPEeWFORLZt5AZxw@0-legend",
        "answer": ["0.4866340991575271", "0.5957617603708059"]
      },
      {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "0P4IVXHVEeWuyAoV4azvow@0-legend",
        "answer": ["0.8975118224043399", "0.3660189067013562"]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "title": "Advanced Writing",
    "link": "https://www.coursera.org/learn/advanced-writing/exam/HcYie/plagiarism-quiz/attempt",
    "questionList": [
      { "id": 0, "question": "teJnHyZ5EeWKdCIACymP9g@0-legend", "answer": [] },
      {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "yr6lCSZ8EeWKdCIACymP9g@0-legend",
        "answer": ["0.48438215791247785"]
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "-2BYWSaBEeWKdCIACymP9g@0-legend",
        "answer": ["0.6063900329172611"]
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "PLQhOCaCEeWc0yIACxCI4Q@0-legend",
        "answer": ["0.34568264731206", "0.6220712424255908"]
      },
      {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "vulqCCaCEeWBKCIACyeusQ@0-legend",
        "answer": [
          "0.8681975181680173",
          "0.7430240861140192",
          "0.15581901650875807"
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "title": "Advanced Writing",
    "link": "https://www.coursera.org/learn/advanced-writing/exam/CPlvf/synthesis-essay-quiz/attempt",
    "questionList": [
      {
        "id": 0,
        "question": "UBkHVXavEeW-GA4WnuJ_pQ@0-legend",
        "answer": ["0.36098358035087585"]
      },
      {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "1lfxCXavEeW-GA4WnuJ_pQ@0-legend",
        "answer": ["0.375405342085287"]
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "q7moh3bZEeWXgwog9OsYJw@0-legend",
        "answer": ["0.5167367474641651"]
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "LXLtiHbbEeWbYxIauobzlw@0-legend",
        "answer": ["0.07793915458023548"]
      },
      {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "imX7ZHbcEeW9DA5hNnbyqw@0-legend",
        "answer": ["0.7627838396001607"]
      },
      {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "jUjlY3beEeWXgwog9OsYJw@0-legend",
        "answer": ["0.03347535524517298"]
      },
      {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "kckrY3bgEeWbYxIauobzlw@0-legend",
        "answer": ["0.5857046009041369"]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "title": "Advanced Writing",
    "link": "https://www.coursera.org/learn/advanced-writing/exam/IFp2m/documented-essay-quiz/attempt",
    "questionList": [
      {
        "id": 0,
        "question": "UHmIh3qBEeWkDxKoCqOeWw@0-legend",
        "answer": ["0.8677051598206162"]
      },
      {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "ks9E_H9LEeWDHQ4vkpWa7w@0-legend",
        "answer": ["0.322603469947353"]
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "1L15Tn9LEeWDHQ4vkpWa7w@0-legend",
        "answer": ["0.000021624378859996796"]
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "GRJNo39MEeWeMwpFuOx8Fw@0-legend",
        "answer": ["0.16865977458655834"]
      },
      {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "TlZR_H9MEeWeMwpFuOx8Fw@0-legend",
        "answer": ["0.9581037354655564"]
      },
      {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "hlKYXX9MEeWDHQ4vkpWa7w@0-legend",
        "answer": ["0.24234112002886832"]
      },
      {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "vx9OSX9MEeWDHQ4vkpWa7w@0-legend",
        "answer": ["0.3944349051453173"]
      },
      {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "AmT8in9NEeWeMwpFuOx8Fw@0-legend",
        "answer": ["0.07970589073374867"]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "title": "Introduction to Research for Essay Writing",
    "link": "https://www.coursera.org/learn/introduction-to-research-for-essay-writing/assignment-submission/cYaIj/introduction-to-research-quiz/attempt",
    "questionList": [
      {
        "id": 0,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~z7pry6KBEeWfAgqS8SVRsQ@3!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~uClxFKKCEeWN9w6e5MEYYQ@0-legend",
        "answer": ["0.5533835338428617"]
      },
      {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~z7pry6KBEeWfAgqS8SVRsQ@3!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~fE1jEqKDEeWN9w6e5MEYYQ@0-legend",
        "answer": ["0.20195616013370454"]
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~z7pry6KBEeWfAgqS8SVRsQ@3!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~xD1fQ6KDEeWN9w6e5MEYYQ@0-legend",
        "answer": ["0.8600632499437779"]
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~z7pry6KBEeWfAgqS8SVRsQ@3!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~pCV4q6KEEeWN9w6e5MEYYQ@0-legend",
        "answer": ["0.6031707883812487"]
      },
      {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~z7pry6KBEeWfAgqS8SVRsQ@3!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~44qRJqKEEeWN9w6e5MEYYQ@0-legend",
        "answer": ["0.7708603232167661"]
      },
      {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~z7pry6KBEeWfAgqS8SVRsQ@3!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~GWGt_KKFEeWZ8hIPDIvEyQ@0-legend",
        "answer": ["0.5628231263253838"]
      },
      {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~z7pry6KBEeWfAgqS8SVRsQ@3!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~Veclo6KFEeWWfQpsgGkKtQ@0-legend",
        "answer": ["0.6376685977447778"]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "title": "Introduction to Research for Essay Writing",
    "link": "https://www.coursera.org/learn/introduction-to-research-for-essay-writing/assignment-submission/nNAez/practice-quiz/attempt",
    "questionList": [
      {
        "id": 0,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~Opta36KTEeWQ8xJEkcqusQ@8!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~rwcJKaNrEeWWfQpsgGkKtQ@0-legend",
        "answer": ["0.457892709877342"]
      },
      {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~Opta36KTEeWQ8xJEkcqusQ@8!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~pRxR3qNsEeWWfQpsgGkKtQ@0-legend",
        "answer": ["0.5255386098288"]
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~Opta36KTEeWQ8xJEkcqusQ@8!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~aCBfXKNuEeWWfQpsgGkKtQ@0-legend",
        "answer": ["0.8827512650750577"]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "title": "Introduction to Research for Essay Writing",
    "link": "https://www.coursera.org/learn/introduction-to-research-for-essay-writing/assignment-submission/Gszpk/doing-research-quiz/attempt",
    "questionList": [
      {
        "id": 0,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~Hw8oCY_zEeWXtQobFfGinQ@8!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~NfrGE4_zEeWF3xJlg5A0Nw@0-legend",
        "answer": []
      },
      {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~Hw8oCY_zEeWXtQobFfGinQ@8!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~yRV2X4_zEeWegQonxsk-Tw@0-legend",
        "answer": []
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~Hw8oCY_zEeWXtQobFfGinQ@8!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~VDY5Ao_0EeWegQonxsk-Tw@0-legend",
        "answer": []
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~Hw8oCY_zEeWXtQobFfGinQ@8!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~izLQ25JFEeWF3xJlg5A0Nw@0-legend",
        "answer": []
      },
      {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~Hw8oCY_zEeWXtQobFfGinQ@8!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~SnVvyp1GEeWnCBIcwGSxuQ@0-legend",
        "answer": []
      },
      {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~Hw8oCY_zEeWXtQobFfGinQ@8!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~mYIZvZ1GEeWnCBIcwGSxuQ@0-legend",
        "answer": []
      },
      {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~Hw8oCY_zEeWXtQobFfGinQ@8!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~NG7ut53YEeWCbBII-AbRmw@0-legend",
        "answer": []
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "title": "Introduction to Research for Essay Writing",
    "link": "https://www.coursera.org/learn/introduction-to-research-for-essay-writing/assignment-submission/5Opzb/practice-quiz/attempt",
    "questionList": [
      {
        "id": 0,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~Lz8G_6KTEeWDoBIAZyegZQ@3!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~-wpTwqN0EeWZ8hIPDIvEyQ@0-legend",
        "answer": ["0.1429963819682598"]
      },
      {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~Lz8G_6KTEeWDoBIAZyegZQ@3!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~n1c4kaN2EeWWfQpsgGkKtQ@0-legend",
        "answer": ["0.9371046130545437"]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "title": "Introduction to Research for Essay Writing",
    "link": "https://www.coursera.org/learn/introduction-to-research-for-essay-writing/assignment-submission/fGiy3/practice-quiz/attempt",
    "questionList": [
      {
        "id": 0,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~MzQ1qKKTEeWWzA4qzDH3hQ@3!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~ywnaeqNbEeWWfQpsgGkKtQ@0-legend",
        "answer": ["0.9643495881464332"]
      },
      {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~MzQ1qKKTEeWWzA4qzDH3hQ@3!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~J2WnC6NcEeWWfQpsgGkKtQ@0-legend",
        "answer": ["0.42182184755802155"]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "title": "Introduction to Research for Essay Writing",
    "link": "https://www.coursera.org/learn/introduction-to-research-for-essay-writing/assignment-submission/4WjQv/language-for-research-quiz/attempt",
    "questionList": [
      {
        "id": 0,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~lHLLRJ1KEeWQ1hL8ZLsXXw@8!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~pf5fTZ1KEeWnCBIcwGSxuQ@0-legend",
        "answer": ["0.44104340369813144"]
      },
      {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~lHLLRJ1KEeWQ1hL8ZLsXXw@8!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~5joBoJ1KEeWnCBIcwGSxuQ@0-legend",
        "answer": ["0.7284766139928252"]
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~lHLLRJ1KEeWQ1hL8ZLsXXw@8!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~En19AZ1LEeWnCBIcwGSxuQ@0-legend",
        "answer": ["0.03165677888318896"]
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~lHLLRJ1KEeWQ1hL8ZLsXXw@8!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~PfVD851LEeWnCBIcwGSxuQ@0-legend",
        "answer": ["0.32854722416959703"]
      },
      {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~lHLLRJ1KEeWQ1hL8ZLsXXw@8!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~aC43cp1NEeWnCBIcwGSxuQ@0-legend",
        "answer": ["0.7885178793221712"]
      },
      {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~lHLLRJ1KEeWQ1hL8ZLsXXw@8!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~a9kv-Z4MEeWbtQ4H8ZmubQ@0-legend",
        "answer": ["0.6722373191732913"]
      },
      {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~lHLLRJ1KEeWQ1hL8ZLsXXw@8!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~zUWtm54MEeWbtQ4H8ZmubQ@0-legend",
        "answer": ["0.766177369048819"]
      },
      {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~lHLLRJ1KEeWQ1hL8ZLsXXw@8!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~_oQkH5-eEeWWfQpsgGkKtQ@0-legend",
        "answer": ["0.9315933221951127"]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "title": "Introduction to Research for Essay Writing",
    "link": "https://www.coursera.org/learn/introduction-to-research-for-essay-writing/assignment-submission/QH3qt/practice-quiz/attempt",
    "questionList": [
      {
        "id": 0,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~IZFJ5aKTEeWnGg4RLqnd6w@3!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~t9HoyaNWEeWN9w6e5MEYYQ@0-legend",
        "answer": ["0.06021587853319943"]
      },
      {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~IZFJ5aKTEeWnGg4RLqnd6w@3!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~W2sCtaNXEeWWfQpsgGkKtQ@0-legend",
        "answer": ["0.25453891372308135"]
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~IZFJ5aKTEeWnGg4RLqnd6w@3!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~OuqOxKNbEeWN9w6e5MEYYQ@0-legend",
        "answer": ["0.41931184637360275"]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "title": "Introduction to Research for Essay Writing",
    "link": "https://www.coursera.org/learn/introduction-to-research-for-essay-writing/assignment-submission/UtIw0/citing-sources-and-formatting-quiz/attempt",
    "questionList": [
      {
        "id": 0,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~SeYi8KEsEeWo6Q41rTrvxw@7!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~5J_ei6KUEeWN9w6e5MEYYQ@0-legend",
        "answer": ["0.2666500473860651"]
      },
      {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~SeYi8KEsEeWo6Q41rTrvxw@7!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~u9aS6KK1EeWWfQpsgGkKtQ@0-legend",
        "answer": ["0.259626061655581"]
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~SeYi8KEsEeWo6Q41rTrvxw@7!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~DIP0dKK2EeWN9w6e5MEYYQ@0-legend",
        "answer": ["0.007261026417836547"]
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~SeYi8KEsEeWo6Q41rTrvxw@7!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~p3LKN6K7EeWWfQpsgGkKtQ@0-legend",
        "answer": ["0.44999573891982436"]
      },
      {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~SeYi8KEsEeWo6Q41rTrvxw@7!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~Yqn3SKK-EeWN9w6e5MEYYQ@0-legend",
        "answer": ["0.9460593145340681"]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "title": "Introduction to Research for Essay Writing",
    "link": "https://www.coursera.org/learn/introduction-to-research-for-essay-writing/assignment-submission/PAVql/practice-quiz/attempt",
    "questionList": [
      {
        "id": 0,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~D97Mo6KTEeW9ZgqZuGAWmQ@4!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~hCFkL6KxEeWN9w6e5MEYYQ@0-legend",
        "answer": ["0.9469325032550842"]
      },
      {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~D97Mo6KTEeW9ZgqZuGAWmQ@4!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~34giVKKxEeWWfQpsgGkKtQ@0-legend",
        "answer": ["0.021334280259907246"]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "title": "Introduction to Research for Essay Writing",
    "link": "https://www.coursera.org/learn/introduction-to-research-for-essay-writing/assignment-submission/89pit/practice-quiz/attempt",
    "questionList": [
      {
        "id": 0,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~FAk8raKTEeWo6Q41rTrvxw@2!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~qSjocaLHEeWWfQpsgGkKtQ@0-legend",
        "answer": ["0.3202891231048852"]
      },
      {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "autoGradableElementId~FAk8raKTEeWo6Q41rTrvxw@2!~SUBMITTER_VIEW_EVALUATION!~gQwEHqLKEeWZ8hIPDIvEyQ@0-legend",
        "answer": ["0.5908107119612396"]
      }
    ]
  }
]
